[Live Forever]
[Episode 13]
You remember everything now, don't you?
You...
Why did you pretend you didn't remember?
Why did you pretend you didn't know me?
Marry him! Marry him!
Director Lin.
How wonderful.
An old dream of the Republican era.
Memories of a past life.
Let go of her hands!
Ning Changyue.
Commander Ning.
Baiwei and I were engaged.
This is between the two of us.
Engaged?
When?
Is it now?
♪ So here is to you ♪
Forget about your
♪ My darling ♪
fragmented memories.
Song Baiwei?
♪ And here is to you ♪
Song Baiwei is just
a pseudonym she casually made up
♪ My friend ♪
when she was an illustrator
for Zhaoxi Newspaper.
♪ Here is to you ♪
Do you know why
she was called Song Baiwei?
♪ My lover ♪
Because when she painted,
there was a pot
of swallowwort on the windowsill.
♪ I'll follow you until the end ♪
Listen carefully.
She has used the name Song Yiqiu
for 3,000 years.
Three thousand years?
♪ So when the fire are burning ♪
You don't know?
Before this,
she was called Ningjia,
Qingwu,
and dozens or hundreds of other names.
♪ And when the light fades away ♪
The days she was called Song Baiwei
were just an insignificant moment
in her long life.
♪ When the sky is falling ♪
♪ I'll never let you be alone ♪
So what if it's a moment?
I can treat her well in every life.
I can love her in every life.
I can give her a moment in every life.
What is this?
A destiny of many lifetimes?
You...
Open your eyes and see clearly.
Do you see it?
She and I are the same kind of people.
For 3,000 years,
she has been my wife.
And she will only be my wife.
And your ecstatic reunion
♪ So here is to you ♪
is nothing but
an insignificant little accident.
♪ My darling ♪
Enough!
♪ And here is to you ♪
Do you decide
who I am?
♪ My friend ♪
♪ Here is to you ♪
Song Baiwei is me.
♪ My lover ♪
Song Yiqiu is also me.
♪ I'll follow you until the end ♪
They are all my names.
They are just my names.
Ning Changyue, you haven't changed at all.
♪ I'll follow you until the end ♪
Song Yiqiu!
Come on.
Tell me what happened.
Is that your new romance?
No.
He is the director
of the Autumn Art Gallery,
an
old friend of mine.
I owe him something.
I can't pay it back now,
so I can only hide.
Then,
isn't Mr. Ning jealous?
He...
He's not jealous.
He just uses wounds to prove
that I belong to him.
Forget it.
Just an ex-husband.
Do you often
run away from home like this
and give Mr. Ning the cold shoulder?
This is nothing.
We've done this before.
I think the longest time before
was 70 or 80 years.
I mean 70 or 80 months.
What's wrong?
I just feel
you guys are wasting too much time.
I used to
have someone I loved very much too.
I thought we would be together forever.
But later,
there was an accident,
and she passed away.
Dr. Xie.
So,
life is unpredictable.
You should cherish
the time with your loved one.
I don't even know
if we're still lovers anymore.
I'm afraid that getting back together
will just be repeating the same mistakes.
Then tell him.
Tell him you're hurting.
If you don't change, face it, or solve it,
of course you'll repeat the same mistakes.
Why aren't you back yet?
What did you mean by what you said today?
Fighting again? Again?
Love for lifetimes.
No.
How can my uncle be defeated like this?
[Lin Huai]
Can I stay at your place for a few days?
Is the fight that serious this time?
What happened
between you two again?
Nothing.
I just don't want to stay at home.
Uncle.
Everyone has their own expertise.
Your problem
needs a professional to solve.
I don't have a problem.
Your search history
from last night still shows
"How can I make
my romantic rival disappear?"
My finger slipped.
Okay, your finger slipped.
But this person is a professional.
She's a little liar.
This is Lin Huai's birth chart.
I want you to find every one
of his destined love ties
and sever them all!
Sever the love ties?
This matter
is a bit difficult.
But you've found the right person.
Five hundred to sever one.
My uncle is not short of money.
Start the reading.
This, this, this...
I... I'll pay for it.
I'll pay. Don't worry, Uncle.
Where does the red thread
of love intertwine?
God of Matchmaking, show us the way.
Where does the red thread
of love intertwine?
God of Matchmaking, show us the way.
Where does the red thread
of love intertwine?
God of Matchmaking, show us the way.
Where does the red thread
of love intertwine?
God of Matchmaking, show us the way.
Where does the red thread
of love intertwine?
God of Matchmaking, show us the way.
Where does the red thread
of love intertwine?
God of Matchmaking, show us the way.
Where does the red thread
of love intertwine?
God of Matchmaking, show us the way.
What's wrong?
Are you sure
you want to sever their love ties?
Use less smoke.
It's bad for your health.
Just do the reading.
They are entangled in every lifetime.
It's an inextricably tangled mess.
They have more love ties
than you could ever count!
This much.
How much?
Two and a half million.
Do we look like idiots to you?
Two and a half million?
Are you out of your mind?
Let's go, Uncle.
The Lantern Festival.
Misty rain.
An umbrella.
And a marriage contract!
I guessed it right.
Watch how I handle you.
So touching.
-You're really giving her the money?
-Here.
So touching.
Read one more person's
romantic fate for me.
Who?
Me
and Song Yiqiu.
So the person in question is here.
Here, take this.
Follow me.
Where does the red thread
of love intertwine?
God of Matchmaking, show us the way.
Where does the red thread
of love intertwine?
God of Matchmaking, show us the way.
Where does the red thread
of love intertwine?
God of Matchmaking, show us the way.
Where does the red thread
of love intertwine?
God of Matchmaking, show us the way.
Nothing.
What do you mean nothing?
There is no red thread between you two.
How is that possible?
The red thread between you two
broke decades ago.
Decades ago?
Could it be...
Today at 6:45 PM,
at the third alley west of Xiafei Road,
someone fired a gun in the street.
Their aim was deadly accurate.
And their methods were ruthless.
Commander Ning, I am innocent.
I swear to God,
no shots were fired
during the suppression of the students.
But that gun came from your patrol team.
My man,
in my territory,
was assassinated on the street,
and students were injured.
Tell me,
who should I hold accountable?
Commander.
These are not our men.
It must be the Japanese or the Green Gang.
They want to frame us.
Whoever it is,
it happened in your jurisdiction.
I will only hold you accountable.
I give you 24 hours
to find them.
Yes, Sir.
Run! Run!
I won't marry him! I won't marry him!
Let me go!
I won't marry him!
Song Yiqiu! Song Yiqiu!
Let me go!
Let go!
Hurry!
Let's go!
I can't walk.
Leave me alone and go!
No.
Burn her!
Burn this witch!
Witch!
Go away!
Stay away!
Qiu.
I worked hard
to climb to this position today
just so you wouldn't get hurt anymore.
Commander Ning,
the 5 patrolmen who killed
the students on the street yesterday
have been arrested.
They said in order to disperse
the rioting students as soon as possible,
they did fire their guns
and injured people.
This is their signed confession.
That was fast.
Injuring people in the street.
Abusing power to kill the innocent.
If it wasn't her,
someone else innocent would have died.
Dismiss these 5 people
and investigate them.
Dismiss and investigate?
Nothing.
[Commander Ning Kills 5 Innocent
Patrol Officers to Avenge His Wife]
Explain.
Explain that you didn't know.
Explain that you did so to protect me.
Explain that they were in the wrong,
and you just did the right thing.
Explain it!
Treating human lives like weeds.
Abusing your power.
Is this your so-called protection?
Commander, why didn't you explain?
It was clearly that police chief
who, to close the case,
tortured and killed those 5 patrolmen.
You have even been
protecting those students.
It's not what Madam thinks.
I didn't kill them,
yet they died because of me.
It has already happened.
There's no need to explain.
You still have the nerve to come here?
Get out!
Coming here with your fake apologies.
You have no conscience!
You will die a horrible death!
Commander.
Don't take it to heart.
These people don't understand.
♪ Can I drift away like this? ♪
♪ Sink beneath the waves ♪
♪ I close my eyes tight ♪
Go away!
What are you doing here?
♪ I weigh every vow again and again ♪
Give my family back to me!
How are a widow
and her child supposed to survive?
♪ Can I drift away like this? ♪
♪ Sink beneath the waves ♪
♪ I close my eyes tight ♪
Commander, this is the last household.
They're the family of Granny Chen,
who came to the commander's residence
to file a complaint.
She passed away from grief 2 days ago.
Only her youngest daughter is left.
Leave the things at the door.
I'm not here to deliver things.